Come real close,
talk to
me slow
Your voice got way,
you don't even know
The soft laugh,
the half smile Those eyes keep me here while
Lights low,
time gone,
still here
All night long, tension in the air
Seeing the calm while I'm seeing the fire
Nobody else ever take me higher
Nobody but you,
keeping me sane
When you say my name, it don't sound the same
I love the way you talk to me
Late at night,
honestly
I love the way you stay with me
You don't leave
I love the way you look at me
Like I'm all you see
Yeah, you keep me alive, you keep me alive
You
keep me alive,
you keep me alive
Every time,
your voice in my head
All night,
yeah
Real ones rare,
but you're still here Every doubt fake,
when you near
When I'm stuck, you pull me through I keep moving on, cause you
You keep talking,
I lean in
Feel your presence on my skin
Seeing the hurt, seeing the hope
You my balance, you my road
Day and night, you stay the same
Pull me closer
when you say my name
I love the way you talk to me
Late at night,
honestly
I love the way you stay with me
You don't leave
I love the way you look at me Like I'm all you see
Yeah, you keep me alive, you keep me alive
Late night talk, no fear Just us here
No mask, no space when you Listening
Your voice so calm, it pull me in
Every little move, yeah, I give in
If it all went dark, I'd still hear you
If I lost my way, I'd still feel you
Heart beats slow when you this close You're the only thing I want the most
Still breathe, still breathe
I love the way you talk to me
Like it's just you and me
I love the way you stay with me
You don't leave
I love the way you loyal to me
Only real thing I see
Yeah, you keep me alive,
you
keep me alive
Late night, your voice that calm, that pull Stay close, your voice, I lose control